The game of Baroness solitaire is an adding game at its heart, and the number you're trying to get to, the sum; is that right, when you add is thirteen.
So ace plus queen, the ace is one; the queen is twelve, that equals thirteen.
The king is thirteen by himself.
So aces are worth one, twos are worth two, three is three; face value until you get up to ten, then jacks are worth eleven, queens, twelve, kings are thirteen, so the king doesn't have to be added to anything.
So, how does that work in a real example?
Well the cards I have dealt at the start of this hand of baroness are an ace, a two, a ten, a ten, and a three.
So, if I want combinations that add up to thirteen, at this point all I have are a three plus one of the tens.
So I'm going to take down this three and this ten.
That adds up to thirteen.
There are no more moves.
What'll I do now?
Next segment.